Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Vero's sudden appearance shocked the black bulls and temple mages alike.
What a creation magic! Now, Poseidon's hammer!
No!
That final hammer spell is no match for my rhinoceros armor.
There's not a scratch on him.
Still not a bad try for a temple mouse. You've earned a prize.
My beast's magic, Bearclaw!
You are insects. I shall not allow you to retain even a shred of hope!
Dark magic! Lightless flash!
Huh? What is this?
Alright, you morons! Listen up! The nasty character just crashed the party. But some things have come up so I can't get to them. You blackheads are gonna have to handle it. Now look! It's time to get serious! Push past your limits!
It seemed the fate of the underwater temple was in the black bulls' hands. And then...
No! We won't give up! We're gonna fight with everything we've got!
Cumber spell! Flame lightning exploding cannon!
You're friends are a lot more powerful than I expected!
You're friends!
You're friends are a lot more...
Oh man...
That combo spell was unbelievably powerful and he survived it without a scratch on him!
That combo spell was unbelievably powerful, and he survived it without a scratch on him.
Magna, luck, it was a real manly effort.
Alright, kid.
Stand your ground!
You can't do this back, everybody get down.
Can't do this back, hey, step back, step back.
運命の凍らみ I'm falling down.
君とかなりとハーモニーはなかっこに置き去りのまま.
君の強気の香りを丸く心に引き継ったまま.
待ってるだけじゃもう足りない.
Get through it back!
まっかり抱きしめ.
明日始まつるえ.
Get through it back!
光灯して.
まっくらの魔法って.
Get through it back!
ララララララララ lala.
barnTime.
eraララララララ...
誰が喧嘩の映画を掴Podして.
you pathetic weaklings i gave you a chance and that was all you could do except your despair
ah the puny knight with the anti-magic sword we meet again brat it's one of them
the eye of the midnight sun this is a stroke of luck since you're here i can repay you for all
the pain you caused licht you'll wind up just like these insects at my feet they're not insects
my superiors
listen their job was to take you down and now that job is passed to me
so this scratches the result of a blow from an anti-magic sword to be fair if it had been
anybody else it would have sliced right through and it accomplished more than those other mages
special combo move yeah well that's just the beginning now let's talk about those magic
stones you people want so bad that's right we know what you're after i don't have to tell you
anything runt you're just garbage to me a piece of trash unloved by mana garbage huh now come on
take another swipe at me you won't fare any better than your feeble friends did this beast man even
took out dad his power reserves are like nothing i've ever seen before he's surrounded by waves of
magic his body constantly guarded by them these fools i'll have plenty of time to look for the magic stone
after i massacre every last person here that goes for the people outside too i can only hope such
pitiful specimens will be sufficiently amusing to destroy
my family lives here my friends live here i love them all and i won't let you kill them
such power and he barely touched us the way he's attacking is he reading our key
he's so fast reading his is almost pointless wow that was awesome i didn't realize how powerful
your dance magic was when we were fighting earlier you must have been really holding back and so were
you i didn't know that you had a second sword how tedious sluggish moves glancing blows but what
should i expect from magicless trash and underwater scum you're pathetic now you're asking for it you
overgrown furball we'll do whatever we have to bring you down
that's my boy kato give that beast man everything that you've got look at that kid still acting like
nothing scares him
even from here i can feel the magic the air is practically on fire with it
now look it's time to get serious push past your limits all right captain i guess you mean business
too bad i'll have to put the wine away for now
this is getting worse by the second if i run into that monster and try to fight him he'll kill me but
it if i run off and hide somewhere like i want to do yami will kill me what do i do
i'll take the fun
damn it i was trying to get this over with quickly so i could go see marie
this delay is absolutely unacceptable
hello magic knight you're in for it now unfortunately you're about to be pitted against
the eye of the midnight sun's top chain mage whoever this marie is i'll make sure you never see her
again making a threat like that is a good way to end up dead that's it mirror magic reflect
great nice try but my chain magic immediately senses when attack spells have been cast and counters them
chain magic scorpio chain
come on move faster at this rate you're not going to last very long
you think pretty highly of yourself or a damn minion mirror magic real double oh no whatever
shall i do with an extra target my one chain can't possibly keep up it's a good thing i've got two
in that case reflect refrain oh hey what are you gonna do with those things
die
i told you what threats like that would get you
you had me worried for a second there you irritate me now chain magic heavy chain
to pay you back these lovelies will crush you into nothing
damn he's fast
there's no use running away weakling damn it he looks and talks like an idiot so i thought he'd be easy to
deal with but he's strong
so where are you hiding now
i hate to say it but his magic is solid on both attack and defense if there's any opening here it's with
the caster himself he's underestimated me letting his guard down but i've already played my real double card
so what now
come out come out wherever you are i can tell you're a black bull just from the pathetic resistance you're
putting up your squad is a bunch of pitiful cowardly little misfits shut your mouth dumb looking jerk there you are
i don't you can play the same trick twice did you
so scary save me your brilliant plan failed you idiot and now you'll die you're the idiot here
there's another one
now mirror magic large reflector ray
but how i already defeated your clone well too bad for you that wasn't my clone yeah you dummy
you fell for it you fell for it i used my transformation magic to trick you by turning
into goshen it totally worked he was a tough opponent too tough it's a good thing gray showed up
so thank me already
quit acting like a freak while you look like me or die
i don't have as much power left as i'd like but we still have to defeat the remaining enemies
yes sir
i'm so super sorry about this guess i twisted my ankle
this is ridiculous at least change into something that isn't me
i know a crab they have plenty of legs
oh no if i transform so soon it would use up magic power can't waste that can we
hold on why i'm sure it was right around here aha that away
little hork this way you eat your cake is with your hands
dome head where the hell she's sleeping
don't know she was like that when i found her
even that greedy glutton could be a help against the eye of the midnight sun let's wake her up
oh no we're gonna die
these vines are draining away my magic power
ah i'm getting weaker by the second my vine trap magic bind vine
oh two identical faces someone's using transformation magic you bastard
oh no oh no oh no oh no another one well lucky me two of you knights for the price of one
it won't be long now before my vine magic renders you just as useless as this poor fellow here
no stop please don't let us go
my goodness how easy simply cast my trap magic and let you dimwits wander blithely into them with no
help from me that's it i just wait until you're drained of power and then you're all mine
couldn't be more effortless damn he's got my grim war too i can't produce any mirrors
was he using her as bait hey five head wake up
i know they're both of them i have idea we're trapped here and she's taking a cat nap
no let go please stop i don't want to die even if we could fight back this one can only use
transformation magic useless both of them i'll just have to do something before i run out of magic
all by myself we're squad mates and friends aren't we and that means when we fight i protect you and
you protect me then nobody can take either of us down that's right i can't forget what i learned
on that mission is stealing my magic power and i'll never get it back why are you just hanging
there do something already and we're gonna die will you shut up think how do we fight this guy
i've got a chameleon with zero offense and a bottomless pit who's dead to the world
oh yeah there's nothing i like better than a big old hunk of meat hey gray i have an idea
you don't stand a chance i doubt you could have defeated me before and now that my vines have
drained away more than half your power you're even less equipped to challenge me you know what i got
to admit i'm kind of impressed you're pretty strong for an old man what i'll have you know i'm only 20.
there's no time to hesitate let's do this okay here goes ah what is that hey doom head wake up
somebody's trying to steal your dinner what are you gonna do about it what would i want with
that thing i don't even eat meat you step away from the food such power from someone so small
on the inside she's a beast all right i'll just suck away your magic power too luckily i've already
said trap magic over there
cut with creation magic strike of the sleeping sheep
strike one
we're saved
Meep Meep!
Aaaaaah!
Hold on!
Tako!
This is insane!
Aaaaaah!
I hate to admit it, but when she actually focuses, her attacks are unreal.
And you… you can do a lot more than I thought.
Huh?
You aren't the first person I've seen with the power to transform themselves.
But that rock… I've never known anybody who could transform objects too.
Seems like you could maybe… do a bit more with it.
Meep! Meep! Meep! Meep! Meep! Meep! Meep! Meep!
Well…
What?
I used more magic than I realized!
My transformation's breaking up!
What?
Grey's transformation's fading?
Aaaaaah!
That's right!
We've never seen Grey's true form before!
I wonder what it'll look like!
Not the big guy with the smoke?
Aaaaaah!
What?!
You're a tiny little girl?!
Oh my gosh! How could this happen?!
It's even worse than those creepy vines!
It looks so embarrassed!
Don't look at me, please!
Why would I look at you when I can gaze upon the face of my angel Marie?
The sight of her face will restore my strength!
Seriously? He's not even a little interested?!
Wow! So that's what you look like! Not what I expected!
I hate letting anyone see my real self!
I wish the meaning with the vines would just kill me!
I can't stay like this! Please help!
Aw, come on! What's the matter? You're so cute!
Stop!
Now, I've always wanted to ask, how old are you, really?
Um, I'm 24?
Huh?! You're five years older than me?! No way!
I simply refuse to believe that you and I are the same age, Glutton.
What?! You mean you're 19 too?!
I'm almost out of magic power.
I wonder how that feisty brat is coming along.
You had some hope left. An attack like that is child's play to me! You'll have to do a lot better.
Not yet.
Looking at you disgusts me.
Fighting with objects you aren't even worthy to touch.
You don't have so much as a sliver of hope.
And do you know why?
One, you're weak to long-distance attacks such as throws,
especially when it comes to non-magical objects.
Two, you're physically strong but still outmatched by one whose strength has been magically enhanced.
Get to the point already!
And three, you don't know where to give up.
You think if you hang on long enough you're bound to find some way of turning the fight in your favor.
So you persist in your reckless attacks against foes you can't defeat,
and leave yourself open to mortal wounds.
It makes me sick to see the Demon Slayer sword and the Demon Dweller sword in the hands of undeserving filth like you!
It's all you want. It won't change anything.
You and your worthless friends never had a chance of defeating me.
Go on, Howl. Embrace your despair!
No one ever protected anybody by getting up!
What?
And I thought animals were supposed to have good hearing.
What he said was no one ever protected anybody by giving up!
For a young man in the morning
どうして眠れない
こんなBad day by by Blackverse
呟いても消えない強い不安
For hours lately
I've been crying for hours, baby
I wish you were here
君がくれた
All those letters
読み返すたびに
The pain's gone
一人じゃない
Cause we're a perfect task
離ればなれ
でも
繋がる
Believe in you
いつもそばに
感じているから
Closer to me
And I'd hope I follow you
君に行く
You know you're not alone
Cause we're a perfect task
Closer to me
And I'd hope I follow you
君に行く
いつもそばに
私がいるから
Closer to me
And I'd hope I follow you
君に行く
Closer to me
Magical Sleuth Charmy
Hello everyone
The great magical sleuth Charmy here
You're joining me just in time
To help me solve a mystery
And uncover what dastardly villain ate my cake
On my honor as a master detective
I will determine who done it
That's easy, you did it
The scene of the crime, my room
This is a brazen thief
Look, it's you, okay
But the scoundrel made a big mistake
They left this handprint behind
That looks a lot like your handprint
The thieving cake eater
Yeah, that's you
It was me
Well, yeah
The ocean is a marvelous restaurant
Let's finish this up already
And get to eating all those yummy fish
Black Clover page 46 awakening
My magic is gobbling up the bounty of the Z
So fast
N